Cloud-Native SOC Investigation Note

Event:
Grafana and Loki were used to review Kubernetes workload logs.

Tools:
Grafana
Loki
Promtail

Namespace reviewed:
soc-workloads

Query used:
{namespace="soc-workloads"}

Observed result:
Grafana/Loki returned logs from the Kubernetes workload namespace, including the suspicious-container simulation.

Evidence files:
evidence\loki-grafana-pod-status.txt
evidence\soc-system-services.txt
screenshots\grafana-loki-soc-workloads-logs.png

Security meaning:
Centralized logging allows SOC analysts to investigate workload behavior, review container output, correlate events with alerts, and support incident timelines.

SOC workflow stage:
Workload generated logs -> Promtail collected logs -> Loki stored logs -> Grafana displayed logs -> Screenshot captured -> Investigation note created
